{"id": "5f544b21-9f0b-4d01-b46c-c5999be87550", "text": "/* Delivery to CLEMENTI AVE 4 billed to Queensway Secondary School */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "CLEMENTI", "AVE", "4", "billed", "to", "Queensway", "Secondary", "School", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "9ccd8df3-85f3-4634-a421-4d79ffa520c5", "text": "# Ship to HOUGANG ST 61", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "HOUGANG", "ST", "61"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "ce4c3d57-fb6c-43d5-9e25-09812856f6f0", "text": "# Ship to SIN MING AVE", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "SIN", "MING", "AVE"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "b71f7658-01a9-4fae-b90a-cfade122a2e5", "text": "// Partner: SIA Engineering Company (POC: Charlotte Cain)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "SIA", "Engineering", "Company", "(", "POC", ":", "Charlotte", "Cain", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "af26d587-7f7a-461f-b5e6-18492d6b3e79", "text": "git fetch --all --prune", "tokens": ["git", "fetch", "-", "-", "all", "-", "-", "prune"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "42982dcf-def8-4285-8468-b337d7dbc5fa", "text": "\"name\": \"service-prod\"", "tokens": ["\"", "name", "\"", ":", "\"", "service", "-", "prod", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "94b8d583-f0e7-44a0-93f7-c42dab1d40ee", "text": "// Contact Wu Gang for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Wu", "Gang", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "918e60ad-182f-40a9-ac4f-1273da886a5d", "text": "# Ship to BUANGKOK GREEN", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "BUANGKOK", "GREEN"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "2e84974a-dccf-4d0e-910e-80dad076f790", "text": "/users/GarciaKarin.karin_garcia/docs", "tokens": ["/", "users", "/", "GarciaKarin", ".", "karin_garcia", "/", "docs"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "86236a4b-a302-49ca-9de0-b1e1ecdb8bc4", "text": "const owner = \"Loke Wan Tho\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Loke", "Wan", "Tho", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "7b64410a-148f-4c8a-82cc-5caef4043ef1", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"YISHUN ST 42\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "YISHUN", "ST", "42", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "2d8baa6b-5998-41c8-a718-f3ac98415054", "text": "import os, sys", "tokens": ["import", "os", ",", "sys"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "e9971e49-3d54-40bc-91f7-0d42ec77c74c", "text": "const MingJohn = garciaPriyaName;", "tokens": ["const", "MingJohn", "=", "garciaPriyaName", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "b53228ba-6a47-40de-85c3-0fca2b9bec64", "text": "// Partner: S N N Builders (POC: Mohd Fared Jainal)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "S", "N", "N", "Builders", "(", "POC", ":", "Mohd", "Fared", "Jainal", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "e46a62a4-261d-46cf-834d-9eedbc5f05d7", "text": "const owner = \"Low Swee Chen\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Low", "Swee", "Chen", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "7932d2c0-3e0e-4332-b2b1-cafff47afaf1", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"TECK WHYE AVE\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "TECK", "WHYE", "AVE", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "1a5ccd1f-3dc6-4a7f-b281-f48d0850c1a4", "text": "// Partner: Matthew & The Mandarins (POC: Jesmine Ho Yen Wah)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "Matthew", "&", "The", "Mandarins", "(", "POC", ":", "Jesmine", "Ho", "Yen", "Wah", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "8bf30a95-89f3-4b20-b4d6-b634f6f955ea", "text": "etag = \"a978868a2691\"", "tokens": ["etag", "=", "\"", "a978868a2691", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "7ff1dbc6-38cd-4f63-9931-b1ca506e94e9", "text": "\"company\": \"360 Entertainment Productions\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "360", "Entertainment", "Productions", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "f77b7697-0ace-4c11-8f82-dcc69d7bb33d", "text": "import os, sys", "tokens": ["import", "os", ",", "sys"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "89c43109-ad2c-4343-8079-556f899bc4b8", "text": "address = \"INDUS RD\"  # point person: Joachim Alexandre Marie Meneuvrier", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "INDUS", "RD", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Joachim", "Alexandre", "Marie", "Meneuvrier"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "898eddc0-ca4b-4478-979a-5c11b8f0607f", "text": "address = \"KG KAYU RD\"  # point person: Xu Meizhen", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "KG", "KAYU", "RD", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Xu", "Meizhen"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "d259c6c0-f938-4de5-9500-f1432252fa91", "text": "// Contact Jazmyn Chelliah for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Jazmyn", "Chelliah", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "9ee128c3-ea80-4d64-bfb7-dab4d1a769a0", "text": "const owner = \"Lee Jin Pyn\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Lee", "Jin", "Pyn", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "4166b85c-6c52-4788-a7ad-afc08a2a84d5", "text": "/* Assigned to Zulkhairi Zulkiflee at ANG MO KIO AVE 4 */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Zulkhairi", "Zulkiflee", "at", "ANG", "MO", "KIO", "AVE", "4", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "4da5d02e-ec93-4ec6-a277-f513908510d6", "text": "// Partner: SGS Group of Companies (POC: Tan Yoong Kek)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "SGS", "Group", "of", "Companies", "(", "POC", ":", "Tan", "Yoong", "Kek", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "5380becb-bc14-49dc-b69a-34fcb7020f08", "text": "https://svc.cluster.local/wei_nair-anna_rahman", "tokens": ["https", ":", "/", "/", "svc", ".", "cluster", ".", "local", "/", "wei_nair", "-", "anna_rahman"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "1c9e1f06-3325-4557-83d3-354684552b6a", "text": "// Partner: VA Tech Wabag (POC: Lok Meng Chue)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "VA", "Tech", "Wabag", "(", "POC", ":", "Lok", "Meng", "Chue", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "decb34c5-63b9-4e13-8556-837cd33963ab", "text": "/* Assigned to Dipa Ein Siak at JLN DUSUN */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Dipa", "Ein", "Siak", "at", "JLN", "DUSUN", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "d04898bb-c802-4107-b35c-e9e166864bd7", "text": "// Partner: Singapore Commodity Exchange Limited (POC: Ang Kong Hua)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "Singapore", "Commodity", "Exchange", "Limited", "(", "POC", ":", "Ang", "Kong", "Hua", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "3a4d5066-5395-4926-babf-10e9e6fda95a", "text": "const owner = \"Zaheera Hashim\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Zaheera", "Hashim", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "caa4b248-3d67-48c5-a4a1-29801b99f31c", "text": "address = \"SEMBAWANG WAY\"  # point person: Ronald Milne", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "SEMBAWANG", "WAY", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Ronald", "Milne"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "0d8db771-2e06-4925-b6db-c02a54023836", "text": "/* Assigned to Christopher Gnanaretnam Thevathasan at WOODLANDS DR 42 */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Christopher", "Gnanaretnam", "Thevathasan", "at", "WOODLANDS", "DR", "42", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "0c41337e-3373-48c5-bac1-d970f5648b56", "text": "from garciaChen import KarinMing", "tokens": ["from", "garciaChen", "import", "KarinMing"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "62b44fe4-b819-410c-98ed-1d5e1fd37bc1", "text": "\"company\": \"Amara Raja Infra\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "Amara", "Raja", "Infra", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "fcefad57-8f0a-4c3a-a255-e70509eccd65", "text": "// Partner: Federation of Indian Muslims (POC: Bernard Chen Tien Lap)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "Federation", "of", "Indian", "Muslims", "(", "POC", ":", "Bernard", "Chen", "Tien", "Lap", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "4192ca3b-ef3d-4363-9c00-32ff6d02e175", "text": "const SaraRahul = priya_tanName;", "tokens": ["const", "SaraRahul", "=", "priya_tanName", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "58933605-b41b-4b69-9a48-df7ac440a2a5", "text": "const owner = \"Akhbar Nawab\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Akhbar", "Nawab", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "4d4c19c4-67fb-4e83-afa8-1da0d1659cdd", "text": "const vendor = \"G. K. Goh Holdings\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "G", ".", "K", ".", "Goh", "Holdings", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "23ab36e3-54d4-410d-a3c3-5e1c75b20007", "text": "/* Assigned to Poh Seng Song at PUNGGOL EAST */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Poh", "Seng", "Song", "at", "PUNGGOL", "EAST", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "517268f0-59d5-475a-ad8e-2629af4b5386", "text": "tobiLee.wei_sato.wei_chen", "tokens": ["tobiLee", ".", "wei_sato", ".", "wei_chen"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "8ae9f182-1f4e-4204-8790-9c679544e436", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"CHAI CHEE AVE\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "CHAI", "CHEE", "AVE", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "46bc2a64-04e2-4045-810f-21dc68b4055f", "text": "#define Rahuldubois 1024", "tokens": ["#", "define", "Rahuldubois", "1024"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "d92eeb78-7c09-449b-8658-b594a12a21ad", "text": "import os, sys", "tokens": ["import", "os", ",", "sys"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "ddffcb94-1306-4461-a415-5c998b0bf9e2", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"CANBERRA ST\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "CANBERRA", "ST", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "6bb890d4-d34c-4159-afdc-6a017d77c2a7", "text": "kubectl get pods -n default", "tokens": ["kubectl", "get", "pods", "-", "n", "default"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "9fcc7171-7bb4-4ee2-8a5f-8dfedf9cc25b", "text": "address = \"WOODLANDS DR 44\"  # point person: Gentle Bones", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "WOODLANDS", "DR", "44", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Gentle", "Bones"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "6f5eb7ba-cd46-4630-9077-3bd11a1afcb0", "text": "\"company\": \"The Kothari Wheels\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "The", "Kothari", "Wheels", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "d915e78e-987d-40c3-91ed-71da5ee1e6aa", "text": "const owner = \"Ng Eng Hen\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Ng", "Eng", "Hen", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "514bc089-84ae-4a21-a5cf-2bda63b24eed", "text": "make build && make test", "tokens": ["make", "build", "&", "&", "make", "test"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "3ccd202b-b695-406d-9790-ac7d856794f6", "text": "/* Assigned to J. H. Low at BUANGKOK GREEN */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "J", ".", "H", ".", "Low", "at", "BUANGKOK", "GREEN", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "0ecb4a6f-a761-448b-90cf-6ce7a4dcdb8c", "text": "const vendor = \"Sika\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "Sika", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "ceaaf0a0-55e9-49c8-8515-7c838e5005ac", "text": "// Contact Yeong Yoon Ying (Civil servant) for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Yeong", "Yoon", "Ying", "(", "Civil", "servant", ")", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "e540553a-d2b2-46ab-bb28-07e60786c82e", "text": "address = \"BT BATOK ST 51\"  # point person: Thang Tran Phenh", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "BT", "BATOK", "ST", "51", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Thang", "Tran", "Phenh"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "4c52356d-6147-4992-9a88-7354900030f9", "text": "// Contact Allan Chan Pow Kieng for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Allan", "Chan", "Pow", "Kieng", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "9807cc23-5cb4-4694-a5fa-cfeedc25bd45", "text": "from karin_karin import tan_rahul", "tokens": ["from", "karin_karin", "import", "tan_rahul"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "0c7f8795-e83d-4f4a-8605-ab2a9d8cd5eb", "text": "// Contact Lu Huiyi for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Lu", "Huiyi", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "0f690d5f-9ef7-4ca3-a660-f830e6891af4", "text": "/* Delivery to JURONG GATEWAY RD billed to Polycab Wires */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "JURONG", "GATEWAY", "RD", "billed", "to", "Polycab", "Wires", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "a7467215-5e64-483d-8b1c-0a357c23907c", "text": "# Ship to YISHUN AVE 2", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "YISHUN", "AVE", "2"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "78bbce14-954a-462d-9990-c088a7faa861", "text": "address = \"CANBERRA WALK\"  # point person: Prof. Lily Kong", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "CANBERRA", "WALK", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Prof", ".", "Lily", "Kong"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "12b6416c-fc83-44c1-9396-e7b19492ec57", "text": "// Contact Goh Jin Theng for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Goh", "Jin", "Theng", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "e2fff142-2e34-4ef5-a069-ca7b595ca014", "text": "/* Assigned to Mrs Cecilia M. Nayar at BOON TIONG RD */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Mrs", "Cecilia", "M", ".", "Nayar", "at", "BOON", "TIONG", "RD", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "53c6e74a-3902-4263-9047-ad28b8b042ad", "text": "git fetch --all --prune", "tokens": ["git", "fetch", "-", "-", "all", "-", "-", "prune"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "bea4d429-0c93-4911-8b05-300302b3b4bd", "text": "# Ship to ZION RD", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "ZION", "RD"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "f05561e1-122f-432e-b0aa-cb2b20978def", "text": "# Ship to ANG MO KIO AVE 5", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "ANG", "MO", "KIO", "AVE", "5"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "68991b8b-2a0c-459c-a848-30f3996dc2d4", "text": "address = \"CHOA CHU KANG DR\"  # point person: Rosa Daniel", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "CHOA", "CHU", "KANG", "DR", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Rosa", "Daniel"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "80856164-2fef-428a-bbc1-a343dc4d9423", "text": "/* Delivery to WOODLANDS CIRCLE billed to Qatar Petroleum */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "WOODLANDS", "CIRCLE", "billed", "to", "Qatar", "Petroleum", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "60720e91-61ba-4e6c-95a1-94281570495d", "text": "# Ship to BEO CRES", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "BEO", "CRES"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "cad5f90b-ad12-4ff7-8038-15232ed1deae", "text": "\"company\": \"Juma Al Majid Group\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "Juma", "Al", "Majid", "Group", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "0803ea48-06fe-4b71-a10f-6517c7b5eca7", "text": "const owner = \"Low Sze Wee\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Low", "Sze", "Wee", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "734e6ad1-8fb0-4ce9-b378-20a3ab815447", "text": "address = \"BISHAN ST 11\"  # point person: JG", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "BISHAN", "ST", "11", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "JG"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER"]}
{"id": "3191988f-4fcf-48c4-a9a9-954eacc4acdd", "text": "# Ship to MEI LING ST", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "MEI", "LING", "ST"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "a4e90cf4-8041-4ad6-b287-65c1e750998b", "text": "const owner = \"General Mohan Singh\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "General", "Mohan", "Singh", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "7ce25f8e-74f6-4894-aaba-88ccb09e3651", "text": "address = \"SENGKANG WEST AVE\"  # point person: Tay Khoon Hean", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "SENGKANG", "WEST", "AVE", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Tay", "Khoon", "Hean"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "89057043-41b3-4938-b251-55f56bfc8711", "text": "// Contact Subbu Venkatraman for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Subbu", "Venkatraman", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "5d59d96d-f811-4a11-8638-985cb1d0547c", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"HOUGANG AVE 1\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "HOUGANG", "AVE", "1", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "0cd80a85-d90c-461a-bd31-fd0f6f3ed6b0", "text": "const vendor = \"Singapore Teochew Sim Clan Association\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "Singapore", "Teochew", "Sim", "Clan", "Association", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "66b07c72-f4dc-4fa7-8270-db4bc08e2f03", "text": "\"company\": \"Sterling\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "Sterling", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "50577911-aae5-4d74-9b57-737a35c77f8a", "text": "const vendor = \"Ayushakti Ayurved\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "Ayushakti", "Ayurved", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "69fca21c-c56c-4288-999a-c2374c4bb9a6", "text": "import os, sys", "tokens": ["import", "os", ",", "sys"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "43ae9600-ac0f-41a9-bb05-c258f3be4f2b", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"CLEMENTI ST 12\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "CLEMENTI", "ST", "12", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "485a9c56-ea4d-4e15-b0bc-a9132c306021", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"SERANGOON NTH AVE 4\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "SERANGOON", "NTH", "AVE", "4", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "013a588e-3fe7-497c-b941-535944de7b21", "text": "const vendor = \"Panasonic Life Solutions...\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "Panasonic", "Life", "Solutions", ".", ".", ".", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "fa1fdc1a-8882-45c2-83eb-427557fb1b75", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"GANGES AVE\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "GANGES", "AVE", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "e91970d2-6c65-4b00-8a60-7a7ecb0e8d41", "text": "# Ship to KIM KEAT LINK", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "KIM", "KEAT", "LINK"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "e2bb6ad3-86ec-40e8-8548-1884081f447a", "text": "/users/garciaRahul.SatoPriya/docs", "tokens": ["/", "users", "/", "garciaRahul", ".", "SatoPriya", "/", "docs"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "f49c634c-fc94-4463-bbc9-2311bab92083", "text": "const owner = \"Lim Siam Kwee\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Lim", "Siam", "Kwee", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "05fdb186-575c-4ca1-9eca-449bba992bba", "text": "/* Assigned to Indra Shahrir Ismail at GLOUCESTER RD */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Indra", "Shahrir", "Ismail", "at", "GLOUCESTER", "RD", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "071d2892-36d4-469a-a8a5-95dfcc115c7c", "text": "/* Delivery to ANG MO KIO ST 31 billed to Dhampur Sugar Mills */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "ANG", "MO", "KIO", "ST", "31", "billed", "to", "Dhampur", "Sugar", "Mills", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "1b577230-2965-4d31-8b12-acbdf36e19e3", "text": "// Partner: Minda Automotive Solutio... (POC: C. C. Chin)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "Minda", "Automotive", "Solutio", ".", ".", ".", "(", "POC", ":", "C", ".", "C", ".", "Chin", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "78a6e9d1-490f-4e7a-9dfc-9c66f1e3abce", "text": "// Contact Nazry Bahrawi for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Nazry", "Bahrawi", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "fcb8c89b-c594-4056-95ff-25f7eeb287d9", "text": "address = \"BT BATOK WEST AVE 7\"  # point person: Karen Tan Puay Kiow", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "BT", "BATOK", "WEST", "AVE", "7", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Karen", "Tan", "Puay", "Kiow"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "b6d1eee0-0b3b-4e53-9ba6-42588489731f", "text": "\"company\": \"gateway-prod\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "gateway", "-", "prod", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "f37b5ef4-04a0-48ce-baa1-2b9bab069983", "text": "const vendor = \"Supertech\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "Supertech", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "5fdd75ad-23bd-4a42-b16c-1f83c3fb38ae", "text": "// Partner: King George's Medical Un... (POC: Dr Kozo Ando)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "King", "George", "'", "s", "Medical", "Un", ".", ".", ".", "(", "POC", ":", "Dr", "Kozo", "Ando", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "d49fa06b-b7b1-46bc-b388-a04d33b5e582", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"CANBERRA VIEW\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "CANBERRA", "VIEW", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "e76b47e7-262f-4938-8e94-015e1cf0d25c", "text": "addr = 0x4d65d7aade25", "tokens": ["addr", "=", "0x4d65d7aade25"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "5ae291da-c20c-459d-aeb0-465596e33156", "text": "\"company\": \"Joister Infomedia\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "Joister", "Infomedia", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "ec765b79-1de1-4d74-af03-34f02e969fac", "text": "# Ship to JURONG GATEWAY RD", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "JURONG", "GATEWAY", "RD"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "e0c5b490-c5b5-4f87-ab8b-83d2e624a9c7", "text": "/* Delivery to SIMEI LANE billed to Malabar Group Of Compani... */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "SIMEI", "LANE", "billed", "to", "Malabar", "Group", "Of", "Compani", ".", ".", ".", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "2696a52f-7021-4e2c-a457-48fc4479fbc0", "text": "address = \"CAMBRIDGE RD\"  # point person: Limin Hee", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "CAMBRIDGE", "RD", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Limin", "Hee"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "2d725be0-f8db-41ba-a147-d13e3f4ad9af", "text": "# Ship to BISHAN ST 11", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "BISHAN", "ST", "11"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "c1deaacd-fbb8-4e42-a2e6-b9ddf64521d3", "text": "import os, sys", "tokens": ["import", "os", ",", "sys"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "020dd9e8-6fa5-469f-86a9-74be09a68d52", "text": "const vendor = \"The Andhra Sugars\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "The", "Andhra", "Sugars", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "cde38b62-c8b0-4d7d-8d6a-d5a4dff7a084", "text": "/* Assigned to Ridzwan Dzafir at SIMEI ST 4 */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Ridzwan", "Dzafir", "at", "SIMEI", "ST", "4", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "c53d1a62-0a2f-4fe4-921c-1ce90add8fd5", "text": "// Contact Awi Rafael for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Awi", "Rafael", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "bd8e2466-f458-460b-b34b-5f36e2ae7a1e", "text": "// Contact Sheik Alau'ddin for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Sheik", "Alau", "'", "ddin", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "7e5905af-1e19-4981-952a-6e355bba4235", "text": "address = \"JURONG WEST ST 61\"  # point person: Eiffel Chong", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "JURONG", "WEST", "ST", "61", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Eiffel", "Chong"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "38ccd767-5bc5-44f7-bca3-453d22a3f38d", "text": "const owner = \"Lina Ng\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Lina", "Ng", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "4bb4a64a-fa4f-494b-9e53-6656fc02f791", "text": "const owner = \"Shashi Jayakumar\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Shashi", "Jayakumar", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "7c3af2e8-e719-49c9-881e-df4a152753d7", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"CHOA CHU KANG LOOP\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "CHOA", "CHU", "KANG", "LOOP", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "8d5e5d88-41bc-436f-9c0c-5cc58ae3a7af", "text": "/* Delivery to KG ARANG RD billed to Uneecops Technologies */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "KG", "ARANG", "RD", "billed", "to", "Uneecops", "Technologies", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "def3affd-3b67-44ec-a4e9-b5030a12d4fd", "text": "// Contact Sitoh Yih Pin for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Sitoh", "Yih", "Pin", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "ceaf57bc-6dd3-41ed-bfad-ffce2e99ba51", "text": "/* Delivery to TECK WHYE LANE billed to Enrich IT */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "TECK", "WHYE", "LANE", "billed", "to", "Enrich", "IT", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "1eeed7f7-c88f-4c68-8d4d-fa262df5a6d5", "text": "/* Assigned to Chia Wai Hon at CHOA CHU KANG CRES */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Chia", "Wai", "Hon", "at", "CHOA", "CHU", "KANG", "CRES", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "df29e82d-d25c-40da-b7eb-b974d8214471", "text": "// Contact Abdol Azez bin Satta @ Aziz Satar for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Abdol", "Azez", "bin", "Satta", "@", "Aziz", "Satar", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "d4a21b86-3a9d-4cb8-86ed-3499328f802d", "text": "/* Delivery to BT PURMEI RD billed to Shri Ram Murti Smarak Co... */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "BT", "PURMEI", "RD", "billed", "to", "Shri", "Ram", "Murti", "Smarak", "Co", ".", ".", ".", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "b32c1a02-3e86-46cc-b3b0-7ac5d065fcfc", "text": "const vendor = \"MPH Bookstores (Singapore)\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "MPH", "Bookstores", "(", "Singapore", ")", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "3c06b29f-228d-49ce-8b6c-0ba222f9e85f", "text": "/* Delivery to JLN BAHAGIA billed to Chinese High School Old Boys' Association */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "JLN", "BAHAGIA", "billed", "to", "Chinese", "High", "School", "Old", "Boys", "'", "Association", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "917b8738-91b0-4af0-964b-7c879e283422", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"TAMPINES AVE 8\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "TAMPINES", "AVE", "8", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "58be0212-f7ab-4dd9-96b1-ce2bde9744a7", "text": "const garciaLee = JohnTobiName;", "tokens": ["const", "garciaLee", "=", "JohnTobiName", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "e5a641c4-ad0e-41cd-aaad-0931c7506de9", "text": "// Contact Punch Coomaraswamy for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Punch", "Coomaraswamy", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "a35d6970-0cf9-492f-8868-293a60715451", "text": "const vendor = \"Kajaria Ceramics\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "Kajaria", "Ceramics", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "bce4a203-2203-4a84-8c11-6da4be0b1227", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"CORPORATION DR\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "CORPORATION", "DR", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "06e02409-b728-4abd-8328-97b71a9abe06", "text": "/* Assigned to Balakrishnan Ramasamy at WELLINGTON CIRCLE */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Balakrishnan", "Ramasamy", "at", "WELLINGTON", "CIRCLE", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "d413c738-382f-49d9-96eb-0d8261635439", "text": "// Partner: Vivimed Labs (POC: Rita Zahara)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "Vivimed", "Labs", "(", "POC", ":", "Rita", "Zahara", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "7fbe187b-e072-41a3-8eee-2941d60c893e", "text": "const owner = \"Edison Liu T.\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Edison", "Liu", "T", ".", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "e3ef108c-8627-49e1-acda-6e22e3036229", "text": "# Ship to JURONG WEST ST 62", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "JURONG", "WEST", "ST", "62"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "f13791f3-0876-4865-947f-6834a910690c", "text": "git fetch --all --prune", "tokens": ["git", "fetch", "-", "-", "all", "-", "-", "prune"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "382b01c0-bd9b-439f-8359-a2ab1f3b7ad7", "text": "namespace Satoanna.Ming_John;", "tokens": ["namespace", "Satoanna", ".", "Ming_John", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "ae7ca633-1b0f-4bf8-bf15-4a189625f646", "text": "// Partner: CallHealth (POC: Perinpanayagam James)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "CallHealth", "(", "POC", ":", "Perinpanayagam", "James", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "0a9204cf-826e-42ee-8b6d-032c9ce2c2b0", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"LOWER DELTA RD\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "LOWER", "DELTA", "RD", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "bf2bcd24-b44f-4349-81e2-9a6049d1a600", "text": "kubectl get pods -n default", "tokens": ["kubectl", "get", "pods", "-", "n", "default"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "5a790f29-600e-4f07-bf87-87548eff5a18", "text": "\"company\": \"UCO Bank\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "UCO", "Bank", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "4818bb35-414d-45ac-9b90-faa035a978f3", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"SERANGOON NTH AVE 1\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "SERANGOON", "NTH", "AVE", "1", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "99427999-fd4b-480a-8b99-d3b6f1a2e543", "text": "git fetch --all --prune", "tokens": ["git", "fetch", "-", "-", "all", "-", "-", "prune"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "e2559398-941b-4fd5-a949-decb176d2b76", "text": "from karinAnna import garcia_wei", "tokens": ["from", "karinAnna", "import", "garcia_wei"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "f0a614f0-242d-4393-a207-64d9f953cbe2", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"HENDERSON CRES\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "HENDERSON", "CRES", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "6a6e581e-f020-4c5d-a24c-2b5bd3fde28c", "text": "address = \"BEDOK NTH RD\"  # point person: Phua Kin Siang", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "BEDOK", "NTH", "RD", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Phua", "Kin", "Siang"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "91ea9316-ee85-4504-a917-ff62c1b577a1", "text": "/* Delivery to QUEEN'S RD billed to Neuland Laboratories */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "QUEEN", "'", "S", "RD", "billed", "to", "Neuland", "Laboratories", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "4cb1f3ff-de61-49ee-a6df-0df9bc03bda4", "text": "// Partner: Lotus Hospital (POC: Victor Fernando R. Ocampo)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "Lotus", "Hospital", "(", "POC", ":", "Victor", "Fernando", "R", ".", "Ocampo", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "75e333d6-05c0-4520-ae26-2351557a2cb3", "text": "const owner = \"D. J. Dave\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "D", ".", "J", ".", "Dave", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "46257964-9fb3-4104-a253-3e8092c63146", "text": "\"company\": \"Reliance Cement Company\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "Reliance", "Cement", "Company", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "edffb9d4-5d5c-4e80-b911-e9448d94685b", "text": "public class MingrahmanController { }", "tokens": ["public", "class", "MingrahmanController", "{", "}"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "e9db00a1-b668-43bb-a712-fab8eb4b5aca", "text": "/* Delivery to JELAPANG RD billed to Orient Technologies */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "JELAPANG", "RD", "billed", "to", "Orient", "Technologies", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "a86ea141-e059-4d9d-a914-75f458793764", "text": "address = \"YISHUN AVE 5\"  # point person: Ben Lai", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "YISHUN", "AVE", "5", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Ben", "Lai"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "e090b09d-a41b-4aee-a505-aece74f51a37", "text": "import os, sys", "tokens": ["import", "os", ",", "sys"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "91465a1b-e551-4e6e-9849-88acb2d6f143", "text": "const owner = \"Janet Ang\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Janet", "Ang", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "83cd1857-5bfd-4542-b56f-c9f2ad32ae48", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"MOH GUAN TER\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "MOH", "GUAN", "TER", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "19ffc1eb-2106-4f7e-9d7b-616d2f4e694f", "text": "from priya_anna import johnAnna", "tokens": ["from", "priya_anna", "import", "johnAnna"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "acbc5b97-2423-4423-a61d-96e9e2060639", "text": "// Contact Koh Hoon Teck for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Koh", "Hoon", "Teck", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "c723679d-e4ea-4196-a0fd-76e8cb65ea99", "text": "const owner = \"Xian Jun Loh\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Xian", "Jun", "Loh", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "5d55ddba-6eb8-4ab2-b43a-b50b1f28d110", "text": "/* Delivery to BEDOK NTH AVE 3 billed to Sahara World Management ... */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "BEDOK", "NTH", "AVE", "3", "billed", "to", "Sahara", "World", "Management", ".", ".", ".", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "8333b6f5-c7bc-414a-8ad9-741a1e0cd5f5", "text": "/* Delivery to ANG MO KIO ST 32 billed to Mahindra Trucks & Buses */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "ANG", "MO", "KIO", "ST", "32", "billed", "to", "Mahindra", "Trucks", "&", "Buses", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "5d2c0dac-dff1-4a60-adab-ff9830b549b5", "text": "/* Assigned to George T. James at JURONG WEST AVE 5 */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "George", "T", ".", "James", "at", "JURONG", "WEST", "AVE", "5", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "ad56178a-37ff-4983-a780-a4b4bcb74c8d", "text": "address = \"DEPOT RD\"  # point person: Lim Boon Heng", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "DEPOT", "RD", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Lim", "Boon", "Heng"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "9d92cf7e-284b-4b1b-9b01-efd7403a0400", "text": "address = \"YISHUN ST 61\"  # point person: Rodolfo Severino", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "YISHUN", "ST", "61", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Rodolfo", "Severino"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "67f53bd5-e0a3-49bc-a305-ced74ebb9595", "text": "/* Delivery to PAYA LEBAR WAY billed to Intellect Design Arena */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "PAYA", "LEBAR", "WAY", "billed", "to", "Intellect", "Design", "Arena", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "9829bcca-300b-4686-a57e-b549d8299cca", "text": "// Contact A. Samad Ismail for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "A", ".", "Samad", "Ismail", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "715ee2a6-b7a6-4312-bfe3-cf1d8400d4e9", "text": "\"company\": \"Lionbridge Technologies\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "Lionbridge", "Technologies", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "b5c1d02e-5b5f-4ecc-a529-5c6fcb2921df", "text": "// Partner: Church of Our Saviour (POC: Khairulddin Wahab)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "Church", "of", "Our", "Saviour", "(", "POC", ":", "Khairulddin", "Wahab", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "b266331c-1364-493c-acbc-08a8b882d566", "text": "address = \"CIRCUIT RD\"  # point person: Leslie Fong Yin Leong", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "CIRCUIT", "RD", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Leslie", "Fong", "Yin", "Leong"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "20c43218-e1e3-4ec6-ba28-b094115dd37b", "text": "address = \"MONTREAL LINK\"  # point person: Yvonne Salmon", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "MONTREAL", "LINK", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Yvonne", "Salmon"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "0fd04091-ed4a-4725-95a1-f5b9a7dcefc0", "text": "const vendor = \"Committee on Sporting Singapore\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "Committee", "on", "Sporting", "Singapore", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "106f85a5-f324-4475-a133-a677d2c5f84a", "text": "/* Assigned to Martha Atienza at JLN BT MERAH */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Martha", "Atienza", "at", "JLN", "BT", "MERAH", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "6412d5dd-7adb-4274-8707-0e825fddc589", "text": "/* Delivery to YISHUN AVE 6 billed to Servomax India */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "YISHUN", "AVE", "6", "billed", "to", "Servomax", "India", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "9d206577-59ed-4be0-807b-871e655f55aa", "text": "const vendor = \"Eng Choon Hway Kuan (Singapore)\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "Eng", "Choon", "Hway", "Kuan", "(", "Singapore", ")", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "87c78b97-6ff0-46e5-a295-d9ff2a521424", "text": "\"company\": \"Newton Boys School\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "Newton", "Boys", "", "School", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "79e74d24-7cc2-4909-a1eb-4942cc708eb3", "text": "# Ship to FERNVALE ST", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "FERNVALE", "ST"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "ca022fe6-03ee-4882-9842-0165ba17b59f", "text": "const owner = \"John Michael Gullick\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "John", "Michael", "Gullick", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "2674942b-1034-4eca-99d0-0695c77ee5ac", "text": "etag = \"9de0dcd94dca\"", "tokens": ["etag", "=", "\"", "9de0dcd94dca", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "7e5a95a1-7813-4b3b-a76f-a7f047f7901e", "text": "// Partner: Public School (POC: Daniel Goh Pei Siong)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "Public", "School", "(", "POC", ":", "Daniel", "Goh", "Pei", "Siong", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "aca101be-5206-488e-845e-28dd6eb6cc14", "text": "// Partner: MediShield Life Review Committee (POC: Zurinah Hassan)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "MediShield", "Life", "Review", "Committee", "(", "POC", ":", "Zurinah", "Hassan", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "077e7c78-fc41-4b47-9b73-215604d36992", "text": "const owner = \"Lydia Lim\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Lydia", "Lim", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "9ef331ea-178e-400e-9e32-90c36d4590ff", "text": "/* Assigned to Leonard Tan at BEDOK NTH ST 1 */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Leonard", "Tan", "at", "BEDOK", "NTH", "ST", "1", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "9920db44-dab8-43e9-a3a0-7608cf1577ce", "text": "// Partner: TriFid Research (POC: Adeline Ooi)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "TriFid", "Research", "(", "POC", ":", "Adeline", "Ooi", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "820ebb8e-adc8-4241-8e8f-80e66d6f284d", "text": "/* Delivery to UPP CROSS ST billed to Moody International */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "UPP", "CROSS", "ST", "billed", "to", "Moody", "International", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "c7a27fb5-0b2a-4b4b-b5f5-1b118509026c", "text": "sato_rahman.weiWei.rahul_lee", "tokens": ["sato_rahman", ".", "weiWei", ".", "rahul_lee"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "bc227ba0-68f5-483a-b98c-a28273e56107", "text": "// Partner: Inspiredge IT Solutions (POC: Hua Thanh Binh)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "Inspiredge", "IT", "Solutions", "(", "POC", ":", "Hua", "Thanh", "Binh", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "60654299-3044-4115-8185-c1c068f18de7", "text": "// Contact Rajendra Gour for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Rajendra", "Gour", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "6c846acf-56c3-4797-a011-04b6fba0523d", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"TAMPINES ST 11\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "TAMPINES", "ST", "11", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "2c591a70-b186-4b7f-b920-18e0bd1fd61c", "text": "address = \"WOODLANDS DR 14\"  # point person: Subhas Anandan", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "WOODLANDS", "DR", "14", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Subhas", "Anandan"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "229be078-67d6-4a07-91b3-30b631e3453b", "text": "// Contact Yeow Seng Yong for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Yeow", "Seng", "Yong", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "178b8db7-9a83-48ae-b5bd-09a4b1beed7c", "text": "// Contact Sim Kee Boon for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Sim", "Kee", "Boon", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "28075b1c-a67d-4b19-a9e9-900fc5b0a2f3", "text": "/* Delivery to BEDOK RESERVOIR RD billed to TestingXperts */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "BEDOK", "RESERVOIR", "RD", "billed", "to", "TestingXperts", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "41efd70e-87b0-4a61-bf14-af74e3e382cc", "text": "address = \"TAMPINES ST 83\"  # point person: Aloysius Doraisamy", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "TAMPINES", "ST", "83", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Aloysius", "Doraisamy"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "713e505f-c288-4a6a-bf62-b0ac4eca37a9", "text": "/* Assigned to Natahar Bava at PUNGGOL EAST */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Natahar", "Bava", "at", "PUNGGOL", "EAST", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "91f03447-6172-4793-b96d-23cc8c5a36f0", "text": "\"company\": \"Sreenidhi International ...\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "Sreenidhi", "International", ".", ".", ".", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "20ed43ff-a421-4b42-9816-ce27d81630c7", "text": "/* Delivery to TAMPINES CTRL 1 billed to Miracle Software Systems */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "TAMPINES", "CTRL", "1", "billed", "to", "Miracle", "Software", "Systems", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "77a47d28-bf69-42d0-8a40-8f00adcd9875", "text": "const vendor = \"Secure Value\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "Secure", "Value", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "c264496e-3dfa-43ee-9f16-a00eca8e0895", "text": "/* Assigned to Low Kim Pong at PASIR RIS ST 13 */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Low", "Kim", "Pong", "at", "PASIR", "RIS", "ST", "13", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "a5e35d00-6a91-49a6-9275-db2fcb4be669", "text": "/* Delivery to NTH BRIDGE RD billed to Robert Bosch Engineering... */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "NTH", "BRIDGE", "RD", "billed", "to", "Robert", "Bosch", "Engineering", ".", ".", ".", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "3a7fc257-5ea9-445c-b44c-dc2431f90e27", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"TAMPINES ST 81\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "TAMPINES", "ST", "81", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "3082adb5-ec48-4f7a-a4db-269a65f9d442", "text": "# Ship to BOON TIONG RD", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "BOON", "TIONG", "RD"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "9745057a-2f88-404d-a57b-f1d06fc7896e", "text": "// Contact Abigail Huang for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Abigail", "Huang", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "93083eda-5848-4071-ae41-c8cc4589fa68", "text": "const owner = \"Tan Ching Yam\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Tan", "Ching", "Yam", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "d567b925-de9a-439d-92b9-5e345033452f", "text": "// Contact M. K. Kumar for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "M", ".", "K", ".", "Kumar", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "d967457d-76c6-4f9a-880d-effedcbdce4a", "text": "// Partner: Koyo Bearings India (POC: E. J. Vass)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "Koyo", "Bearings", "India", "(", "POC", ":", "E", ".", "J", ".", "Vass", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "3ca2c548-4141-46df-b9da-f7f8f3f0732d", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"ZION RD\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "ZION", "RD", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "e17f5a4e-c364-48a3-9670-3895e6651c47", "text": "const owner = \"Mrs T. Kulasekaram\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Mrs", "T", ".", "Kulasekaram", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "fbbeaedc-1fb6-480d-97fa-a8c230447d3b", "text": "# Ship to JURONG WEST CTRL 3", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "JURONG", "WEST", "CTRL", "3"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "51914f0a-ed14-46d8-97a7-3734dc7dc9a5", "text": "// Contact Theresa Wong for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Theresa", "Wong", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "bdf8a856-7dbd-4720-9abf-6a6d5d1dfbbf", "text": "/* Delivery to JURONG WEST ST 91 billed to Mahindra Homes */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "JURONG", "WEST", "ST", "91", "billed", "to", "Mahindra", "Homes", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "49c4e896-d672-4366-97a2-7d912429a016", "text": "/users/sara_sato.john_ming/docs", "tokens": ["/", "users", "/", "sara_sato", ".", "john_ming", "/", "docs"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "793ecc6d-1e1b-4ef0-bbb0-ad30a7a84aba", "text": "address = \"WOODLANDS ST 41\"  # point person: John Angus Bethune Cook", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "WOODLANDS", "ST", "41", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "John", "Angus", "Bethune", "Cook"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "bd28cb9e-2fd6-4b8e-9f8d-3814c5798205", "text": "// Partner: Changi Airports International (POC: Danny Kwok Wynn Ye)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "Changi", "Airports", "International", "(", "POC", ":", "Danny", "Kwok", "Wynn", "Ye", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "b279441f-4f63-42e7-b8cd-774b4d3ed067", "text": "\"company\": \"smartData Enterprises\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "smartData", "Enterprises", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "4fa4f2a5-3904-43d6-b6f2-31c5dfdafefd", "text": "git fetch --all --prune", "tokens": ["git", "fetch", "-", "-", "all", "-", "-", "prune"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "aeb60405-aa6a-4c93-99c9-f0439b9ca767", "text": "\"company\": \"ingest-stage\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "ingest", "-", "stage", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "2d5ac240-f2e5-478d-aa3c-a75e2b4f88a2", "text": "/* Delivery to TIONG BAHRU RD billed to Maneesh Pharmaceuticals */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "TIONG", "BAHRU", "RD", "billed", "to", "Maneesh", "Pharmaceuticals", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "0eae1320-5f0c-40d6-bac4-013e69a7b432", "text": "/* Delivery to CHOA CHU KANG CTRL billed to Bhagwati Products */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "CHOA", "CHU", "KANG", "CTRL", "billed", "to", "Bhagwati", "Products", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "5522c35b-5c44-4f96-be78-40a32135c556", "text": "// Contact Kernial Singh Sandhu for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Kernial", "Singh", "Sandhu", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "733fc797-55f9-4e2a-b708-02402cdd8f5b", "text": "/* Delivery to HOUGANG AVE 5 billed to Cement Manufacturing Com... */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "HOUGANG", "AVE", "5", "billed", "to", "Cement", "Manufacturing", "Com", ".", ".", ".", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "be49b94a-d90f-47fa-afa3-c993c8bdee76", "text": "address = \"YISHUN ST 31\"  # point person: Mak Pak Shee", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "YISHUN", "ST", "31", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Mak", "Pak", "Shee"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "fe365427-9127-4393-802e-4071de345bba", "text": "const owner = \"Ilamaran, Patteral\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Il", "", "ama", "", "r", "", "an", "", ",", "Pa", "", "tte", "", "r", "", "al", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "6c26b1ef-490c-4eb0-98f0-bb5a4d0ae802", "text": "/* Delivery to BT BATOK ST 51 billed to EU Centre in Singapore */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "BT", "BATOK", "ST", "51", "billed", "to", "EU", "Centre", "in", "Singapore", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "ce41c155-c619-46f5-b6a1-96d640e3d910", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"PENDING RD\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "PENDING", "RD", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "3e6b61f4-a618-464c-acbc-735ba500d702", "text": "// Contact Muhammad Hazim Mohd Yusli for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Muhammad", "Hazim", "Mohd", "Yusli", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "6d5f6fd7-218d-40df-a264-1969f9cd41da", "text": "address = \"WOODLEIGH LINK\"  # point person: Wee Bin", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "WOODLEIGH", "LINK", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Wee", "Bin"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "d6cf0e3b-7367-44ec-b5e5-76b06f7031b5", "text": "// Contact Mrs Phyllis Clara Perreau for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Mrs", "Phyllis", "Clara", "Perreau", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "1f885f08-a033-468f-9c30-eecc784277c9", "text": "/* Assigned to Na Govindasamy at BISHAN ST 11 */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Na", "Govindasamy", "at", "BISHAN", "ST", "11", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "52cf3b9d-9dfc-4ba4-834e-48f68f40d67f", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"LIM LIAK ST\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "LIM", "LIAK", "ST", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "ff013898-db59-46fe-8593-ce26b21dece5", "text": "const vendor = \"San Yu Adventist School\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "San", "Yu", "Adventist", "School", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "a9c05f87-8ef9-4d95-a3f6-3410645893b8", "text": "const vendor = \"Drydocks World Dubai\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "Drydocks", "World", "Dubai", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "2d5c4638-da94-46c1-a827-f387ac217230", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"PASIR RIS ST 51\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "PASIR", "RIS", "ST", "51", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "75cd35fb-460c-4f94-8512-ebc1fd34bf58", "text": "const owner = \"S. V. Lingam\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "S", ".", "V", ".", "Lingam", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "19958a8f-e161-4ae4-95f3-dffd1f0748bd", "text": "namespace Johntobi.Wei_Rahman;", "tokens": ["namespace", "Johntobi", ".", "Wei_Rahman", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "186d3702-81d9-4bf9-9810-3496bfa4a853", "text": "// Partner: Dreamz FM (POC: Chelva Retnam Rajah)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "Dreamz", "FM", "(", "POC", ":", "Chelva", "Retnam", "Rajah", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "0921a6f8-a531-4e2e-b73d-5f316d29bbf1", "text": "/* Assigned to Abdul Rahman Mohamad at ANG MO KIO ST 12 */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Abdul", "Rahman", "Mohamad", "at", "ANG", "MO", "KIO", "ST", "12", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "16d34f39-9db1-4f41-8936-5e0e62326a69", "text": "/* Assigned to Sharifah Aishah Osman at BOON KENG RD */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Sharifah", "Aishah", "Osman", "at", "BOON", "KENG", "RD", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "6c7b4f5c-2cb1-4b70-b498-18bd1e56971d", "text": "// Contact Sarah Ang for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Sarah", "Ang", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "27370a1e-5a29-42de-ac76-9c2e76b54ce5", "text": "const vendor = \"Singapore Chinese Amateur Athletic Federation\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "Singapore", "Chinese", "Amateur", "Athletic", "Federation", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "dbde1fdd-aabb-43e0-8232-0ddf1fe14589", "text": "address = \"YUAN CHING RD\"  # point person: Aysha Baqir", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "YUAN", "CHING", "RD", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Aysha", "Baqir"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "88a6d434-11a0-4ae8-8aea-3048129bffaf", "text": "// Partner: LTI (POC: Chong Moong Seng)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "LTI", "(", "POC", ":", "Chong", "Moong", "Seng", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "2e603d29-e66c-4230-91d6-762684414faf", "text": "\"company\": \"Man Infraconstruction\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "Man", "Infraconstruction", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "d5f829b5-8b24-4b05-8fd4-4718e96f57b2", "text": "# Ship to WOODLANDS DR 75", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "WOODLANDS", "DR", "75"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "177cb47e-53b8-4d81-abd8-db1cd4d66325", "text": "const owner = \"Lee See Sin\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Lee", "See", "Sin", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "2425f41f-1ed7-4874-a07d-3021d7e4f31a", "text": "const owner = \"Charmaine Solomon\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Charmaine", "Solomon", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "78b867f0-e5c8-445c-8390-af7dfad537cd", "text": "// Contact Sharon Wee for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Sharon", "Wee", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "7dfc9600-9b51-4574-8801-9373d155f57a", "text": "// Contact Kam Kee Yong for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Kam", "Kee", "Yong", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "68cc7fad-316c-494b-9623-ff07d80f53be", "text": "https://svc.cluster.local/annaTobi-SatoWei", "tokens": ["https", ":", "/", "/", "svc", ".", "cluster", ".", "local", "/", "annaTobi", "-", "SatoWei"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "d8ee537b-20a5-4647-b595-ec48e15d27bc", "text": "/* Assigned to Suhaimi Sukiyar at SENGKANG WEST AVE */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Suhaimi", "Sukiyar", "at", "SENGKANG", "WEST", "AVE", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "89383216-9e6f-4f79-8824-00010ba13298", "text": "/* Assigned to Lim Soo Peng at CANBERRA VIEW */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Lim", "Soo", "Peng", "at", "CANBERRA", "VIEW", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "935fce13-4d07-4848-94f0-912ab4c01bce", "text": "# Ship to SUMANG LINK", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "SUMANG", "LINK"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "60791747-25ae-4372-a15f-45d7d7c684b4", "text": "// Contact Goh Wei Leong for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Goh", "Wei", "Leong", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "f174c5f9-58cc-409d-b564-87c0d48cab00", "text": "address = \"TAMPINES AVE 5\"  # point person: Ronald Benjamin Milne", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "TAMPINES", "AVE", "5", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Ronald", "Benjamin", "Milne"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "35191912-3501-4ed7-a3cf-a619dddef515", "text": "make build && make test", "tokens": ["make", "build", "&", "&", "make", "test"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "758325fc-38d8-4511-926b-7ba81520664a", "text": "// Partner: Hyundai Construction Equ... (POC: Truong Tan)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "Hyundai", "Construction", "Equ", ".", ".", ".", "(", "POC", ":", "Truong", "Tan", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "eb3fe447-359a-4aa7-86b7-bfc1b073c3e5", "text": "/* Assigned to Glory Barnabas at ANG MO KIO AVE 2 */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Glory", "Barnabas", "at", "ANG", "MO", "KIO", "AVE", "2", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "3e2aefb7-6a35-4eba-ad41-cec10e8c37ee", "text": "address = \"GEYLANG EAST AVE 2\"  # point person: Charles Lazaroo", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "GEYLANG", "EAST", "AVE", "2", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Charles", "Lazaroo"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "ebf2d332-b79b-48b4-a253-e6ef3e84fcf0", "text": "# Ship to SMITH ST", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "SMITH", "ST"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "3a67f611-bebb-4cae-be35-8ae8730c4a89", "text": "// Contact Solamalay Namasivayam for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Solamalay", "Namasivayam", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "42d58b8c-7b7a-47f8-8498-abfe76bbf9cc", "text": "// Contact Cheong Koon Hean for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Cheong", "Koon", "Hean", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "0520e520-a4f8-4c57-a0f8-58845cfd3ff1", "text": "address = \"BISHAN ST 13\"  # point person: Ronald MacPherson", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "BISHAN", "ST", "13", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Ronald", "MacPherson"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "0ba5374a-e519-47b2-8ad0-13a274ffdb4e", "text": "/* Assigned to Philip Hoalim Sr at HOUGANG ST 31 */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Philip", "Hoalim", "Sr", "at", "HOUGANG", "ST", "31", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "4594e8fc-3e19-48b1-a46f-3fd6cfbe7cdc", "text": "\"company\": \"Indus Integrated Informa...\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "Indus", "Integrated", "Informa", ".", ".", ".", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "414ed6c8-ecf6-456a-8295-685952dbdd2b", "text": "\"company\": \"Perfect Relations\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "Perfect", "Relations", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "8136e92a-1b17-4ee2-9b0c-8470fb812271", "text": "// Partner: MOLIPS (POC: Liu Ruijin)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "MOLIPS", "(", "POC", ":", "Liu", "Ruijin", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "506e26b5-11cc-423c-89c7-2d369cfead46", "text": "// Contact Ooi Yu-lin for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Ooi", "Yu", "-", "lin", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "90a0425c-7528-4fee-abfa-ab5a6ab197d9", "text": "namespace Tobipriya.Anna_Ming;", "tokens": ["namespace", "Tobipriya", ".", "Anna_Ming", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "98359e25-1b7c-4934-b128-db20cade4376", "text": "address = \"TAMPINES ST 45\"  # point person: N. Veerasamy", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "TAMPINES", "ST", "45", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "N", ".", "Veerasamy"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "57c4a0ac-b3ec-4d5b-becf-bc112b5e9833", "text": "/* Assigned to Chew Tee Pao at HOUGANG ST 91 */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Assigned", "to", "Chew", "Tee", "Pao", "at", "HOUGANG", "ST", "91", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "7a23de7c-2dcd-4df8-8764-12289aeabcb5", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"SUMANG WALK\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "SUMANG", "WALK", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "f4a53e4d-5a83-49ae-bc06-f1e89046c4d1", "text": "\"company\": \"Chitkara University\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "Chitkara", "University", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "808d9694-ce8a-4951-8f87-0e3152aba14c", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"WOODLANDS DR 42\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "WOODLANDS", "DR", "42", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
{"id": "4ca5fbf4-c62a-45dd-8d05-8bca6cac4b62", "text": "// Partner: La opala rg (POC: Benjamin J. Q. Khoo)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "La", "opala", "rg", "(", "POC", ":", "Benjamin", "J", ".", "Q", ".", "Khoo", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "ddcae8ae-1628-46e9-a5a9-f739b28278e9", "text": "/* Delivery to PASIR RIS DR 1 billed to Bharat IT Services */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "PASIR", "RIS", "DR", "1", "billed", "to", "Bharat", "IT", "Services", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "7c62b9bb-395c-46d0-b97f-5e6521aac513", "text": "const owner = \"Nathaniel Soon\";", "tokens": ["const", "owner", "=", "\"", "Nathaniel", "Soon", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "8bdddf10-d842-4637-9e93-45f62fe356e8", "text": "\"company\": \"iSource\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "iSource", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "14ba939e-27af-4da3-95af-6cff21872075", "text": "\"company\": \"Macawber Beekay\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "Macawber", "Beekay", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "2069f2c5-b2ce-44f5-acf0-2d779cdf7c7d", "text": "namespace Nairwei.Satolee;", "tokens": ["namespace", "Nairwei", ".", "Satolee", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "174fcd0f-0ddb-4396-80df-6497563ef5a2", "text": "const vendor = \"Globe Capital Market\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "Globe", "Capital", "Market", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "61ccd827-5e25-4b2a-98ac-f34d5612aaf2", "text": "// Partner: Dance Dimension Project (POC: Han Sai Por)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "Dance", "Dimension", "Project", "(", "POC", ":", "Han", "Sai", "Por", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "2e6b0fac-a54e-422a-a1d2-c29582b4f7fc", "text": "/* Delivery to CANTONMENT CL billed to ComfortDelGro */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "CANTONMENT", "CL", "billed", "to", "ComfortDelGro", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "8a38cf13-faeb-4be2-849d-f469331d34e6", "text": "// Contact Nisha Mehraj for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Nisha", "Mehraj", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "be7cf9bd-0656-4ac2-97b5-d507700f86fb", "text": "\"company\": \"Medico-Legal Society of Singapore\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "Medico", "-", "Legal", "Society", "of", "Singapore", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "d8778731-0906-49e6-8822-e71574150263", "text": "const vendor = \"Duroflex\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "Duroflex", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "d3e4678e-4619-4692-95fd-19f9df676c4c", "text": "// Partner: VSoft Technologies (POC: Liu Xiaoyi)", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Partner", ":", "VSoft", "Technologies", "(", "POC", ":", "Liu", "Xiaoyi", ")"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "9a4869fa-2525-4215-9283-ead33dcd5d4a", "text": "/users/sara_sato.garciaChen/docs", "tokens": ["/", "users", "/", "sara_sato", ".", "garciaChen", "/", "docs"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "06d31d00-563e-4a36-9bcf-0b6ad379088b", "text": "const vendor = \"Irvine Infocom\";", "tokens": ["const", "vendor", "=", "\"", "Irvine", "Infocom", "\"", ";"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "fdf29b9d-67ea-4068-a904-afaf12614dc5", "text": "git fetch --all --prune", "tokens": ["git", "fetch", "-", "-", "all", "-", "-", "prune"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "6e597b4b-add8-4155-8fa8-0422afdf4544", "text": "\"company\": \"Dreamcatcher Pte Ltd\"", "tokens": ["\"", "company", "\"", ":", "\"", "Dreamcatcher", "Pte", "Ltd", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "5833748f-e425-49da-b708-19a719e6b20e", "text": "kubectl get pods -n default", "tokens": ["kubectl", "get", "pods", "-", "n", "default"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "1d203953-d90a-4ee8-af39-8dffa9136af0", "text": "/* Delivery to MARSILING CRES billed to Pulse Pharmaceuticals */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "MARSILING", "CRES", "billed", "to", "Pulse", "Pharmaceuticals", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "a87e29e8-fb60-4362-932c-ad0f896c8923", "text": "// Contact Michael George Wright for access", "tokens": ["/", "/", "Contact", "Michael", "George", "Wright", "for", "access"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "88ed340e-d0ee-42f6-9b36-087505655a10", "text": "/* Delivery to LOR 3 TOA PAYOH billed to Vinove Software & Servic... */", "tokens": ["/", "*", "Delivery", "to", "LOR", "3", "TOA", "PAYOH", "billed", "to", "Vinove", "Software", "&", "Servic", ".", ".", ".", "*", "/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "0135e6b7-0334-4baf-a05d-b6400c304cb5", "text": "address = \"HOUGANG AVE 4\"  # point person: Hadijah Rahmat", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "HOUGANG", "AVE", "4", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Hadijah", "Rahmat"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "a787a8fc-5f69-49a3-be8c-4950f148d037", "text": "address = \"JLN DUSUN\"  # point person: Wu Gang", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "JLN", "DUSUN", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Wu", "Gang"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "1fdf1b1e-0823-4d19-a59c-e1d57a5e1fe8", "text": "address = \"DOVER CL EAST\"  # point person: Muhammad Daniel Kei Bin Muhammad Yazid", "tokens": ["address", "=", "\"", "DOVER", "CL", "EAST", "\"", "#", "point", "person", ":", "Muhammad", "Daniel", "Kei", "Bin", "Muhammad", "Yazid"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "2cd4f1f8-3709-459d-bcb4-5e32851d1f9c", "text": "# Ship to TELOK BLANGAH HTS", "tokens": ["#", "Ship", "to", "TELOK", "BLANGAH", "HTS"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR"]}
{"id": "a24b9542-d76d-4958-b083-db738124c9fa", "text": "\"shipTo\": \"JURONG WEST AVE 3\"", "tokens": ["\"", "shipTo", "\"", ":", "\"", "JURONG", "WEST", "AVE", "3", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "I-ADDR", "O"]}
